<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>School &#8211; Victor Chung</title>
	<atom:link href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/category/school/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio</link>
	<description>Computer Engineer</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 04:36:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/cropped-profilePic-1-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>School &#8211; Victor Chung</title>
	<link>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Technical Report</title>
		<link>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/technical-report/</link>
					<comments>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/technical-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[thevicbro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 04:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[School]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://victorchung838697291.wordpress.com/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[My technical report on&#160;The Potential of Solar Photovoltaics as an Affordable Renewable Energy Source&#160;is a great reflection of my skills and growth as an effective communicator. This was the first term project for my ENG2003 course, and it utilized many of the skills we have learned in the course, specifically about technical writing and the &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/technical-report/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Technical Report"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>My technical report on&nbsp;<em>The Potential of Solar Photovoltaics as an Affordable Renewable Energy Source</em>&nbsp;is a great reflection of my skills and growth as an effective communicator. This was the first term project for my ENG2003 course, and it utilized many of the skills we have learned in the course, specifically about technical writing and the 7 C&#8217;s.</p>



<p>I believe it to be one of the best showcases of my work in ENG2003, as I had spent the most amount of time on it compared to other assignments and activities. It forced me out of my comfort zone, as I had not written any kind of professional report before. Despite this, I had learned a lot about how to present my research and findings in a professional manner such as through charts and diagrams, as well as improve my overall writing skills.</p>



<p>An example of a diagram used can be seen below. This figure represents the percentage of the population in every country which had access to electricity in 2018. This was used to emphasize how although this may not seem to be a problem here in Canada and many other countries, Africa is clearly struggling and falling behind in comparison.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1689" height="894" src="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image.png?w=1024" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image.png 1689w, https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image-300x159.png 300w, https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image-1024x542.png 1024w, https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image-768x407.png 768w, https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/image-1536x813.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /><figcaption>Percentage of population with access to electricity, 2018</figcaption></figure>



<p>Overall the technical report was a great way to get engineers out of their comfort zones, as many of them (including myself) are not the strongest in writing. As engineers we should be expected to clearly describe our creative innovations professionally. This project provided us the chance to do so, and to learn from our mistakes.</p>



<p>This report can be downloaded <a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/termproject1.pdf">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/technical-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Handout</title>
		<link>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/handout/</link>
					<comments>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/handout/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[thevicbro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 04:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[School]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://victorchung838697291.wordpress.com/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The handout assignment was the first ever assignment we had received in ENG2003 and as such, I believe it to be a great reflection of how my skills had grown in terms of being an effective communicator. The assignment consisted of creating two handouts (brochures) on the same topic, but for different audiences (high school &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/handout/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Handout"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The handout assignment was the first ever assignment we had received in ENG2003 and as such, I believe it to be a great reflection of how my skills had grown in terms of being an effective communicator.</p>



<p>The assignment consisted of creating two handouts (brochures) on the same topic, but for different audiences (high school students and experts in the field). This forced us to put ourselves in the reader&#8217;s point of view so that we would choose not just words, but visuals that would appeal to each audience.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.quark.com/assets/beautoful.jpg" alt="Brochure and Catalog Design - Quark"/><figcaption>Source: https://www.quark.com/products/quarkxpress/features/brochure-and-catalog-design/</figcaption></figure>



<p>The main emphasis and goals of the assignment were </p>



<ul><li>Making use of the seven C&#8217;s, such as being concise about what information to use</li><li>The ethos, pathos, and logos behind the statements of the brochures</li><li>Keeping in mind the axioms of communications</li></ul>



<p>Because of this, my brochures were very contrasting visually. My professional brochure had barely any colours, other than pictures and the colour red to help emphasize the dark and sensitive facts and topics. It mostly consisted of black and white, with a plain font and utilizing graphs and diagrams. The high school student-focused brochure was very colourful and used exciting fonts and pictures to help entice the readers to begin and continue reading. I understood that students would not understand many of the more technical terms and may stop reading due to misunderstanding and/or boredom. The colours and design of the professional brochure may even persuade students to not even begin reading the handout in the first place. I also understood that logos would be more effective in the professional brochure (hence the use of graphs and diagrams), while ethos would be the focus in the high school one.</p>



<p>Overall, I found the brochures to be a very fun and interactive assignment to help students use and visualize their understanding in communicating effectively to different audiences. Through the seven C&#8217;s and the use of ethos and logos, I was able to appeal to each audience while still spreading awareness about the same topic.</p>



<p>The individual brochures can be found and downloaded below.</p>



<div class="wp-block-file"><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/the-well-being-of-engineers-hs.pdf">Highschool</a><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/the-well-being-of-engineers-hs.pdf" class="wp-block-file__button" download>Download</a></div>



<div class="wp-block-file"><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/the-well-being-of-engineers-pro.pdf">Professional</a><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/the-well-being-of-engineers-pro.pdf" class="wp-block-file__button" download>Download</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/handout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back of the Napkin Presentation</title>
		<link>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/back-of-the-napkin-presentation/</link>
					<comments>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/back-of-the-napkin-presentation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[thevicbro]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 01:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[School]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://victorchung838697291.wordpress.com/?p=59</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The &#8220;Back of the Napkin Presentation&#8221; was the 4th assignment in ENG2003. It consisted of quickly explaining a concept through writing/drawing and speaking. I chose to showcase this as I believe it to be a great representation of my skills and growth as an effective communicator due to the use and focus of interactivity, vocals, &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/back-of-the-napkin-presentation/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Back of the Napkin Presentation"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The &#8220;Back of the Napkin Presentation&#8221; was the 4th assignment in ENG2003. It consisted of quickly explaining a concept through writing/drawing and speaking. I chose to showcase this as I believe it to be a great representation of my skills and growth as an effective communicator due to the use and focus of interactivity, vocals, and understanding of the audience. </p>



<p>Having to quickly, but accurately describe a complex concept to an audience without any prior knowledge or context is challenging. This assignment pushed our communication skills and helped with working under a time limit, as it simulated quickly explaining a concept (in my case, the engineering behind RAM speed increases) using just the &#8220;back of a napkin&#8221; or pen and paper to another person. This also helped with the skill to explain clearly without a presentation prepared beforehand. </p>



<p>The video can be seen below.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Back of the Napkin Presentation" width="525" height="295" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LhujF2zI2X0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://thevicbro.github.io/portfolio/back-of-the-napkin-presentation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
